strong
reliable trustworthy and forward
thinking
manulife for your future
since our very first establishment in
toronto in 1887
the brand name manulife has progressed
with time
today manulife financial a leading
canadian-based
financial services group serves millions
of customers in 21 countries and
territories worldwide
our presence extends across canada
europe
and emerging markets like asia
with more than 125 years of experience
manulife financial delivers strong
reliable
trustworthy and forward-thinking
financial protection
and wealth management products to our
customers
manulife has been operating in malaysia
since 1963
and is committed to delivering our
promises to meet the financial needs of
our
individual and corporate customers
with a history of financial stability
that spans more than a century
manulife financial is currently listed
in the toronto
new york hong kong and philippines stock
exchanges
and we have strong ratings from five
rating agencies
based on market capitalization we are
one of the largest
life insurance companies in the world
for more than 100 years our customers
can rely on
us wherever and whenever they need us
through our regional support centers
which are strategically located across
malaysia
and our network of professional agents
independent financial planners
and reputable bank partners you can rely
on us
to meet your financial needs
manulife has been a trustworthy partner
to our customers
providing excellent customer services to
ensure that their every need
is taken care of most importantly
we give our word and deliver on our
promises
with our core values of professionalism
providing real value to our customers
acting with integrity demonstrating
financial strength
and being an employer of choice manulife
aspires to be the trusted and most
preferred financial services provider
in malaysia being a socially responsible
company
manulife believes in giving back to the
community
where we do business
with forward thinking and innovative
product solutions
our clients can count on us to think and
plan ahead
to prepare them for their future to
provide better financial services and
solutions to our customers
manulife also leverages on technology to
enhance the communication between staff
and agency members
we are very financially strong property
and our financial situation has
demonstrated very well
we are very reliable company and our
customers find our services reliable
because
we serve them when they leave us and uh
you know we are
a trustworthy company you know we
deliver what we promise
and the last but definitely not the
least you know uh for your future
uh you know forward thinking you know we
uh look into our products
and uh design the product to meet all
the
lifetime meat of our customers and we
are there
for their futures and we definitely will
be with our customer
for the future time of their lifetime
events
manulife's solid financial strength
global expertise
product distinction and integrity remain
undiminished our commitment to our
customers
stakeholders as well as product
innovation
serve as our continued promise to you to
be the most professional
financial services organization in the
world
providing strong reliable trustworthy
and forward thinking solutions to meet
your most
significant financial decisions today
and for your future
you